Next, let's make the strap for knotting.
Click two points on the clothes to determine the approximate length.
Select the rectangular tool to determine the height of the rectangular strip.
Since this strip will be rolled up later,
it is necessary to reduce the particle diameter to increase the surface number,
to prevent the split and conflict of the strip.
Reduce the slope and make the strip narrower.
After finishing,
turn the slope back to 100.
The fabric will be tighter.
Simulate the applied slope.
Copy and paste a strip.
Move one of the strips and rotate it,
so that two strips form an X shape.
The intersection angle is a little smaller,
and the two strips are pulled apart a little.
Do not overlap.
Roll up the edge with a fixed needle.
If it is far away, it will not be tight.
Next, select the fixed needle tool.
In the 2D window,
select the frame to increase the fixed needle.
At the same time, add two strips at the same time.
Apply new fabric to these two strips.
After applying,
turn on the simulation.
After turning on the simulation,
select one side of the fixed needle.
Drag the axis on the positioning ball to rotate the fixed needle.
In the process,
please rotate the fixed needle slowly.
Do not turn too fast at once.
In order to reduce the distance between the strips and the strips,
make the strips stick tighter,
and reduce the thickness of the collision to 1.
When one side of the fixed needle
is turned to about half of the strip,
it is inconvenient to roll it again.
You can rotate to the other side.
After rotating both sides,
the band is not smooth.
You can reduce the size of the excess to 5.
You can rotate to the other side.
Then use the positioning tool
to position the two strips
to the position of the clothing band.
Use the positioning tool
Rotate it to make it parallel to the side of the tree as much as possible.
Draw the inner line on the tree. The length of the inner line should be equal to the length of the bag.
The diameter of the two inner lines should be a little narrower than the length of the tree.
Then delete the fixing pin on both sides of the bag and add a fixing pin on the left side of the bag and on the right side of the other bag.
Now you can see that there is no fixing pin on the right side of the board in the 2D window.
Sew this side to the inner line.
Add a fixing pin on the other side of the board.
After simulation, the bag is more loose.
To make the board tighter, press Shift to select the two fixing pins on the left side.
Then use the positioning ball to rotate these two fixing pins to tighten the board.
Press W and click the board to create a fixing pin.
Click the fixing pin to delete the fixing pin.
Delete the fixing pin on the left side of the other board.
The two fixing pins are now in the inner line.
After stabilizing, gradually raise the slope ratio of the bag to 80%.
If the two sides of the board are rolled up like this in the video, you can delete the pin and simulate it.
Then add the pin.
Due to the structure of the tree belt in ancient times, the belt will be pulled out on one side of the tree belt and rolled back to the front to be worn.
Therefore, we need to use the length of the tree belt as the basis to create the remaining belt board.
Put the two boards together.
From the inner line to the length of the other side of the board as the length.
Create a belt board.
After creating, manually adjust the belt width to match the previous board.
Arrange it to the back arrangement point.
Use the positioning ball to place the board in the position of the tree belt.
Since there is no break point on the side, switch to the free sewing tool and sew the belt to the side of the tree belt.
After sewing, the belt is on the same side of the sewed tree belt.
The sewing line needs to be changed to TIN, so that the sewing line will be flat.
Reduce the diameter of the first particle and the thickness of the middle.
Change the momentum rate to 80%.
On the other side, use the fixing pin to fix it in the 3D space.
After opening the simulation, use the fixing pin to gradually pull the belt to the front of the belt.
For the back end, it is fixed to TIN.
Pull the belt out and you can see the belt.
In the adjustment process, you can open the hard drawing,
and check if there is a red area and the cross-sectional location.
Pull a little bit to make it even.
Unlock and activate the front panel, and delete the fixed pin on the newly created panel.
Combine the two panels together, and check if there is a transitional area in the opening image.
After stabilizing, please delete the fixed pin.
Copy the newly created panel in the 3D window, and paste it near the mirror, and adjust it in 2D, so that there is no overlap between the panels.
Freeze other panels.
Click on the panel in the 3D window to find the horizontal position, and the operation method is the same as on the other side.
If the panel conflicts with the frozen panel, pull it out.
After stabilizing, add a fixed pin.
Then, remove the panels that are in harmony with each other.
Use the fixed pin to pull the two panels closer together.
The length of the panel on this side may not be enough, so pull it a little longer.
Remove the fixed pin and manually drag it closer to the seam.
After sewing, remove the fixed pin and model it again.
Then, open the hard drive to see if there is an over-dodynamization area.
The yellow grid part shows that there will be a certain stretch.
The belt part should be longer.
After stabilizing, open the single-sided display.
Open the single-sided display and check to see if the opposite sides of the same panel are aligned.
If there is a problem with the opposite sides not aligned, as shown in the video, you can use a panel right-click to select the surface flip.
After alignment, use the
RAID tool to select the right panel between the trays to join them.
After alignment, change the shrink value to 100.
Now we start to make the knot part of the bag.
First, add a fixed needle on a whole strip and pull it up a little.
In order to prevent instability, you can reduce the diameter of all the bags to 3.
Draw a rectangle with the same width as the bag.
Reduce the impact thickness and the diameter of the chest.
Use the position to move to the position of the knot, and then use the thread to sew it to the board.
pública
After this is done, it is needed to apply a sf to the back side of the bag.
Keep adjusting the pins to get enough space to put the bag
You can add another pin to form a stable circle between the two panels
Because we need to rotate this panel later, we can delete the original pin and add a whole pin
Then you can use the positioning ball to slowly rotate this whole pin
You can see that the panel is too long, you can move the side of the panel to shorten the panel
Adjust the position of the panel by adding a pin before deleting it
You can see that the panel is too long, you can move the side of the panel to shorten it
When the panel has a certain degree of deformation, remove the fixing pins used to form the circle and simulate again
Adjust the position of the panel by adding a pin before deleting it
Then pull the pin and tighten the guys
When both sides of the bag are done, join them along the sewing line.
Tighten the bag when you pull the bag slowly with the front side of the bag and the front side of the bag.
At the end,
remove the inner line on the bag.
Then,
turn on all the panels to simulate together.
Here you can see that the bag is through.
So,
freeze all other panels to simulate the bag separately.
After the bag is finished,
turn on all panels to simulate together.
To avoid the bag to be scattered,
increase the friction coefficient to increase the friction force of the bag,
which makes it not easy to slide.
This is the first time I ever do this.
The next step is to cut the bottom pin.
Cut the bottom pin on the back side of the bag.
Then,
Re-activate the hair model and open a pre-adjusted posture.